{
  "quiz_name": "Adobe Experience Manager Business Practitioner",
  "topics" :[
    {"key": "Education", "percent":  16},
    {"key": "Architecture", "percent": 26}, 
    {"key": "Business Analysis", "percent":  48}, 
    {"key": "Solution", "percent": 10} 

  ],
  "percentageCorrectForPassingScore": 68, 
  "quiz_questions": [
    {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Location filters let you choose the AEM capability you search in. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Getting Started - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"In addition to Edit what are the available modes when viewing a page?","presented_options":["Layout","Developer","Scaffolding","Customer","User"],"correct_options":["Layout","Developer","Scaffolding"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Getting Started - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which author actions automatically add nodes/properties to the content directory in the JCR? ","presented_options":["Navigating between pages","Adding an image","Creating a page","Editing content"],"correct_options":["Adding an image","Creating a page","Editing content"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Getting Started - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"AEM will run on any version of Java. True or false?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Getting Started - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"The sling:resourceType property for a page points to a page template that defines the basic page structure. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Getting Started - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What occurs when you unpack the AEM jar?","presented_options":["Create a crx-quickstart directory","Installs AEM in the cloud","AEM updates iteslf to the latest version","Installs Java on the local machine"],"correct_options":["Create a crx-quickstart directory"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Getting Started - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"You should install a Java JRE for AEM to work.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Getting Started - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which of the following statements hold true for an authoring environment? ","presented_options":["On an authoring environment, website visitors can post comments on the individual pages or interact with the forums","The authoring environment is usually located behind a company's firewall","Authoring environment provides an easy to use graphical user interface for creating the content","An author in WCM generates the material that which will, at some point, be published to your website"],"correct_options":["The authoring environment is usually located behind a company's firewall","Authoring environment provides an easy to use graphical user interface for creating the content","An author in WCM generates the material that which will, at some point, be published to your website"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Getting Started - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which port does local AEM Author run on default?","presented_options":["8080","8081","4503","4502"],"correct_options":["4502"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Getting Started - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The JCR combines features of relational database systems with conventional file system. What’s the best way to describe the structure of the JCR?? ","presented_options":["Nodes and property-based","HTML-based","Schema-based","Table-based"],"correct_options":["Nodes and property-based"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Getting Started - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"What code does the apps directory pull together from the JCR?","presented_options":["HTML","C++","CSS","Javascript"],"correct_options":["HTML","CSS","Javascript"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Getting Started - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"The most common use of a dispatcher is to cache responses from an AEM publish instance.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Getting Started - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which two items does Omnisearch allow authors to search for?","presented_options":["Tags","Cloud Services","Pages","Workflows"],"correct_options":["Tags","Pages"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Getting Started - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Where in AEM would a user go to link a solution to Adobe Analytics?","presented_options":["The server side","The Adobe Analytics console","The AEM installation page","The admin page"],"correct_options":["The server side"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Working with Marketing Cloud solutions","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Where are Adobe Target's personalization rules run from?","presented_options":["The server side","Locally","Cloud services","The client side"],"correct_options":["The server side"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Working with Marketing Cloud solutions","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If a marketer needs to send 5 millions emails, which email engine should they use?","presented_options":["The Experience Cloud email engine","The Marketing Cloud email engine","The AEM email engine","The Adobe Campaign email engine"],"correct_options":["The Adobe Campaign email engine"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Working with Marketing Cloud solutions","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Adobe Campaign can send personalized SMS messages.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Working with Marketing Cloud solutions","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Where in AEM would you go to configure integration with Adobe Target?","presented_options":["The Adobe Marketing Cloud","Adobe Launch or Adobe Cloud Services for Experience Fragments","IMS security configurations","OSGi configurations"],"correct_options":["Adobe Launch or Adobe Cloud Services for Experience Fragments"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Working with Marketing Cloud solutions","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which Adobe Marketing Cloud solution can pick up a segment created in Adobe Analytics and pass that information to AEM, so it becomes a segment there as well?","presented_options":["Adobe Target","Adobe Campaign","Adobe Social","Adobe Audience Manager"],"correct_options":["Adobe Target"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Working with Marketing Cloud solutions","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"What are some best practices for using AEM with Adobe Campaign?","presented_options":["Implement Adobe Target with AEM for sending email","Do not use javascript or flash","Use or extend the ootb components in AEM designed to work with Campaign"],"correct_options":["Use or extend the ootb components in AEM designed to work with Campaign","Do not use javascript or flash"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Working with Marketing Cloud solutions","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which AEM page property enables shorter, more expressive URLs? ","presented_options":["Vanity URL","Export configuration","Realm URL","On Time"],"correct_options":["Vanity URL"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which design type provide different URLs for different devices?","presented_options":["Fixed design","Responsive design","Adaptive design"],"correct_options":["Adaptive design"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"One of the main reasons for tagging is to quickly and easily classify content for your website.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"When you finish editing a page, you must save it to keep all your changes. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Within the references menu, which sub-menu would you go to to enable Production Ready?","presented_options":["Edit Launch","Edit Properties","Launches","Promote Launch"],"correct_options":["Edit Properties"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Design mode lets you specify the types of components that will appear in Edit mode. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Where is content duplicated when you promote launch content? .","presented_options":["Sidekick","Promotions","Source page","Launch page"],"correct_options":["Source page"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which capability of AEM Sites allows authors to see what has changed on a page for version, launch and language copies? ","presented_options":["Versioning","Timewarp","Page comparison and differential view"],"correct_options":["Page comparison and differential view"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which two configurations on your AEM web console configuration manager do you need to update with your machine IPv4 address? ","presented_options":["Day CQ link externalizer","Day CQ executable locator","AEM campaign integration - configuration","AEM communities analytics component configuration"],"correct_options":["AEM campaign integration - configuration","Day CQ link externalizer"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"You can promote a launch copy of a page to the source copy. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"AEM Sites allows you to compare a re-translated language copy of a page with a previous language copy. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which component in a responsive layout acts as a paragraph system into which you can add other components? ","presented_options":["Content fragment","Aticles list","Carousel","Content fragment"],"correct_options":["Layout container"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Where do you go to add metadata once an asset has been uploaded to the DAM from the web UI? ","presented_options":["Annotate","View properties","Options","Edit"],"correct_options":["View properties"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How do you add a component from the components tab to the paragraph system? ","presented_options":["By double-clicking it","By dragging it","By right-clicking and selecting Add"],"correct_options":["By dragging it"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"How does the DAM appear within the File Manager when you are using the AEM desktop app? ","presented_options":["Network Drive","Shared Drive","Mounted Drive","Local Device","FTP server location"],"correct_options":["Network Drive","Mounted Drive"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Why should you always verify that a newly created newsletter is available on your publish instance?","presented_options":["Because Campaign will try to read it from your publish server","Because Campaign will crash if it is not found","Because Campaign will accept only certain newsletter templates"],"correct_options":["Because Campaign will try to read it from your publish server"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which feature of AEM sites allows you to create a snapshot of a page at a point in time? ","presented_options":["Versioning","References","Timewarp"],"correct_options":["Versioning"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Experience fragments and content fragments share the ability to automatically summarize text with machine learning. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Advanced Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"The Classic UI supports pages and templates created using the template console. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Advanced Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"What can you use the template editor for? ","presented_options":["Positioning components on a responsive grid","Creating static templates","Pre-configuring editable components","Managing template life cycle"],"correct_options":["Positioning components on a responsive grid","Pre-configuring editable components"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Advanced Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which of the following statements are true about editable templates? ","presented_options":["They allow you to define the structure and initial content","They have no dynamic connection with pages","They're created and edited by templates authors or super users","They are the only way to integrate with other Marketing Cloud solutions"],"correct_options":["They allow you to define the structure and initial content","They're created and edited by templates authors or super users"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Advanced Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which of the following actions would benefit the most from the inclusion of an Experience Fragment? ","presented_options":["Creating single use content","Creating raw copy for an editorial page","Creating content that incorporates layout information","Providing content for third-party touchpoints"],"correct_options":["Providing content for third-party touchpoints","Creating content that incorporates layout information"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Advanced Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"What can you define in an editable template? ","presented_options":["The layout of the page for a variety of devices","The policies that define the design properties of a component","The data model for the page","The layout of the native iOS or Android mobile app","The integration with other Marketing Cloud solutions "],"correct_options":["The policies that define the design properties of a component ","The layout of the page for a variety of devices"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Advanced Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"You can use the assets from AEM Assets when building templates in the template editor. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Advanced Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What is the template author responsible for?","presented_options":["Creating components to be used in a template","Creating templates using the template editor","Defining the required access rights"],"correct_options":["Creating templates using the template editor"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Advanced Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"You can select the layout container of an existing AEM web page and convert it into an Experience Fragment. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Advanced Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which of the following can authors import into an existing Content Fragment? ","presented_options":["Videos","PDF Files","Audio clips","Text files"],"correct_options":["PDF Files","Text files"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Advanced Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"After you create a Content Fragment, what is the simplest method of reproducing it with slight modifications? ","presented_options":["Modifying the content fragment template","Creating a variation","Importing that content fragment into an experience fragment","Copying and pasting"],"correct_options":["Creating a variation"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Advanced Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"All workflow process steps that you assign to a user or group of users require user action at different stages of the workflow. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Advanced Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"After you select the pages you want, which menu button allows you to activate those pages in bulk? ","presented_options":["Move","Properties","Manage publication","Edit"],"correct_options":["Manage publication"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Advanced Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"When you create a new workflow model, what two steps are added automatically and can't be deleted? ","presented_options":["Activate page","Flow end","Flow start","Assign user","Flow step"],"correct_options":["Flow end","Flow start"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Advanced Authoring","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Only one member can be assigned to a role in a project master. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Projects","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which of the following options does the AEM calendar offer?","presented_options":["Rich text editor","Search and filter","Colored status icons","Quick access buttons over each item"],"correct_options":["Search and filter","Colored status icons","Quick access buttons over each item"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Projects","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which of the following are true about project masters?","presented_options":["They have predefined properties","They are actionable","They are not actionable","They do not have a start or due date"],"correct_options":["They do not have a start or due date","They are not actionable"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Projects","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which of the following are available view types for items in your calendar inbox? ","presented_options":["Tile","List","Timeline","Column"],"correct_options":["List","Timeline","Column"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Projects","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"What are the three task types you'll find in the inbox? ","presented_options":["Management","Manual","Ad hoc","Work items","Project"],"correct_options":["Ad hoc","Work items","Project"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Projects","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"What can you do within the Inbox in AEM?","presented_options":["Add personal and work contacts","Set item priorities","Monitor workflows","Manage tasks and projects"],"correct_options":["Set item priorities","Monitor workflows","Manage tasks and projects"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Projects","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"The inbox allows you to reassign tasks to different users or user groups. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Foundation Skills - Projects","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Where is most content for an AEM website stored? ","presented_options":["In a database","In Adobe Analytics","In Apache Sling","In a JCR"],"correct_options":["In a JCR"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Infrastructure Overview","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"A client is working on a new project and would like to use Sightly as a preferred templating language. What would be the advantage of using Sightly over JSPs?","presented_options":["Sightly is HTML5","Sightly is secure by default","Sightly provides a much better MVC architecture implementation","Sightly is faster than JSP"],"correct_options":["Sightly provides a much better MVC architecture implementation","Sightly is secure by default","Sightly is HTML5"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Infrastructure Overview","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What information does a marketer have about an ootb AEM site visitor with no additional login? ","presented_options":["Income level","Other sites visited","Browser type","The user's Adobe ID from the Creative Cloud"],"correct_options":["Browser type"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Infrastructure Overview","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"A client wants to set up a globally distributed AEM 6.1 environment. The authors will be spread across the globe, but will work on the same content. What approach should the client use to achieve the above use case? ","presented_options":["Set up clustering with the help of TARMK","Set up an AEM cluster with CRX2","Set up clustering with the help of MongoDB","Set up an AEM cluster with CRX3"],"correct_options":["Set up clustering with the help of MongoDB"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Infrastructure Overview","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"In most AEM architectures, the Dispatcher forwards an un-cached request to which of the following?","presented_options":["An author instance","A publish instance","A web server","Neither the publish instance or the author instance"],"correct_options":["A publish instance"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Infrastructure Overview","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What mechanism can approve content that a digital marketer adds to a website? ","presented_options":["Author server","Publish server","Workflow engine","Apache sling"],"correct_options":["Workflow engine"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Technical Infrastructure Overview","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"When using AEM multi site manager, all content translation must be managed at a central location. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Multi-Sites Manager - Planning a Site","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What is a Live Copy?","presented_options":["Copy of language-specific content that is shared amongst various regions","Copy of website or page that has been published to the publish server","Copy of website or page content for which a live relationship with the original source is maintained","Copy of website or page that will be used as a language copy"],"correct_options":["Copy of website or page content for which a live relationship with the original source is maintained"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Multi-Sites Manager - Planning a Site","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What word or phrase describes the relationship between a source and a Live Copy? ","presented_options":["Blueprint","Language copy","Inheritance","Rollout"],"correct_options":["Inheritance"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Multi-Sites Manager - Planning a Site","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Multi Site Manager comes with its own translation engine. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Multi-Sites Manager - Planning a Site","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which MSM sites/tools can help you generate a live copy from a blueprint? ","presented_options":["MSM control center","crxde lite","Blueprint control center","Create site wizard"],"correct_options":["Blueprint Control Center","Create Site Wizard"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Multi-Sites Manager - Planning a Site","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"When using a blueprint to create a Live Copy, you can identify which branches are required in the Live Copy; however, when creating a Live Copy from a site, you create the Live Copy and then delete the brand. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Multi-Sites Manager - Managing a Site","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Multi-Answer","question_text":"Which of the following triggers can be used to initiate a rollout? ","presented_options":["On deactivation","On delete","On modification","On publication","On update"],"correct_options":["On deactivation","On publication","On modification"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Multi-Sites Manager - Managing a Site","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Once you cancel the inheritance property on a Live Copy, it is permanent. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Multi-Sites Manager - Managing a Site","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which option would you select to create a Live Copy from a blueprint using the Site Wizard in the Touch UI? ","presented_options":["Create a Live Copy","Create a Blueprint","Create a Site","Create a Catalog"],"correct_options":["Create a Site"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Multi-Sites Manager - Managing a Site","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"To configure translation capabilities in AEM, you need to install the appropriate translation package and configure it via AEM cloud services. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Multi-Sites Manager - Managing a Site","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Inheritance is available for a page and a page component; however, it is not available for page properties. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Multi-Sites Manager - Managing a Site","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"You should use the On Modification trigger whenever possible as it provides the best performance for AEM sites. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Multi-Sites Manager - Managing a Site","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True-False","question_text":"A Live Copy can only have one rollout configuration file associated with it. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Business Practicioner"],"question_source":"Multi-Sites Manager - Managing a Site","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }
                           
  ]
}